CIAN RONAYNE

• Senior Analyst, Client Delivery •

ABOUT ME

Highly capable Senior Analyst with over 2 years experience working in paid search & programmatic for some of the worlds largest brands' E-commerce divisions. Certified in Amazon Advertising (search & DSP), currently managing day-to-day operations of a busy team, overseeing \$750,000+ of ad spend per month. A proven self-starter, having embraced and thrived in new roles in both the USA & UK.

EDUCATION

National College of Ireland BA. | Marketing Practice (2nd Class Honors, Grade 1) 2017 - 2020

Killester College of Further Education 2014 - 2015 Diploma of Higher Education | Information Technology (Distinction)

EXPERIENCE

Kepler Group (London, UK)

April 2022 - present

Senior Analyst, Client Delivery

- Manage day-to-day operations of the London team's 25+ e-commerce (Amazon, Criteo, Cdiscount) clients through effective delegation and process innovation/enforcement.
- Act as an Amazon Advertising expert, providing insights & training to colleagues and clients across the business.
- Lead point of contact for sales for the Amazon Unit. Selling in Amazon and the Kepler value proposition to clients.

Flywheel Digital - Ascential plc (London, UK)

August 2020 - April 2022

E-Commerce Media Specialist

- Strategizing and launching advertising campaigns across both AMS & DSP on behalf of clients.
- Continuously optimizing campaigns driving towards KPIs while remaining flexible to adjustments in client's strategy.
- Developing and presenting daily/weekly/monthly reporting, analytics, and performance insights for clients highlighting recent wins, challenges and growth opportunities.
- Serving as an on-call consultant for solutions to any Amazon challenges that may arise via emails, calls, in-person meetings, and reports for clients.
- Remaining ahead of the curve with developments in the Amazon Advertising space in order to provide the best service to clients.

Club Travel Limited (Dublin, Ireland)

October 2018 - July 2020

Digital Marketing Executive

- Maintaining & updating customer databases from 8 different travel agencies.
- Analyzing customer data, and pulling reports in order to prepare & plan for future marketing campaigns.
- Managing the websites of 8 travel agencies, updating web pages with the latest info, utilizing multiple content management systems.
- Launching, optimizing & reporting on campaigns across both Facebook ads & Google ads.
- Copywriting for SEO activity (blogs etc.) and social media activity.

TELEPHONE +44 7857 942677

WEBSITE cian-ronayne.com

EMAIL